

### CONTACT

- +8801730941743
- ✓ Saharulisalm0178@gmail.com

#### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Web Design & Devlopment 84%

Graphic Design 85%

MS Office Program 95%

Database Knowledge 90%

# SAHARUL ISLAM

## COMPUTER ENGINEER

#### **ABOUT ME**

Diploma of computer engineering with more than 1 year of hands-on experience working across the full-stack of Wordpress development and as a data scientist. I've built a few projects by myself and I'm looking for a role where I can grow and learn from other experienced team members.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bangladesh Sweden Polytechnic Institute 2019-2023

**Diploma In Computer Engineering** 

CGPA: 3.50

#### **EXPERIENCES**

Wordpress Developer 2023-2024

#### **Animotion Studio**

- Optimized website loading time performance by 3 times faster
- Created user interfaces across CIM applications using next JS 6 components like grid, tree etc
- Designed and developed more than 140 client websites with WordPress
- Routinely inspect server code for speed optimization

### Academic experience | 2019-2023

- WordPress Developer Skills:
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Shopify, Twitter, YouTube, and WordPress.
- Advance Graphic Design and Tools Use
- Computer Networking & Database